Welcome to this Docuneering ... Business Solutions Department ... product demonstration
The product is our Docuneering ... S1000D version 4.x Publication Module Builder ... and in this video we’re going to do a quick end-to-end demonstration
We start the application from the Start Menu
And this is our S1000D version 4.x ... Publication Module Builder
For this quick end-to-end demonstration ... we have already pre-set an XML source folder which ... for those who are curious ... contains the version 4.1 Bike dataset
The process ... is to now interrogate what source data is contained in this source folder
Click the magnify icon ... to start the interrogation process
As the application starts to analyse files contained in the source folder, the progress bar will display a percentage of task complete
Once all the source folder analysis is complete ... the progress bar will be at 100% ... and a popup will inform you that the process is complete
Click OK to close this popup
The application now knows what files are contained in the source folder ... and the Publication Module dropdown has been populated with a list of all the Publication Modules found in the source folder
Select a Publication Module from this dropdown list and click the “Start PM Builder” button
The progress bar will again display a percentage of task complete and information about the build process is output in the Details window below the progress bar
Once all Publication data has been compiled into a build file ... the build file is passed to the Apache FOP Print Formatter for final processing. A separate command window will open to display the FOP process
Once all FOP processing is complete ... the generated PDF will open to display your Publication
In the case of this demonstration ... we have created a 402 page PDF file complete with bookmarks for navigation
A link will be provided to allow you to download this PDF file for a closer review
This concludes our quick end-to-end demonstration of the Docuneering S1000D version 4.x – Publication Module Builder
Please get in touch with us for any further information